Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - I-L
        - Kassav' - Kassav', 1984; SR-24286; Kassav' (Box 44)
          Catalog # GD 018; A-side Matrix # GD 018 A
        - Kassav' - Lagué moin, 1980; SR-24287; Kassav' (Box 44)
          Catalog # 66791-1; A-side Matrix # FM A 1
          Celluloid
        - Kassav' - Kassav', 1997; SR-24288; Kassav' (Box 44)
          Catalog # 3A 210; A-side Matrix # 3A210A
          3A Production
          France
        - Kassav' - Vini pou, 1987; SR-24289; Kassav' (Box 44)
          Catalog # EPC 460619 1; A-side Matrix # EPC 460619-1 A
        - Kasso - Kasso, 1982; SR-24290; Kasso (Box 44)
          Catalog # 793 821; A-side Matrix # WEA 793827 A10
          Starnight Records
        - KC and the Sunshine Band - I'm your boogie man; Wrap your arms around me, 1976; SR-24291; KC and the Sunshine Band (Box 44)
          Catalog # TKD-32; A-side Matrix # TKD-32-A
        - KC - Space cadet solo flight, 1981; SR-24292; KC (Box 44)
          Catalog # TK-614; A-side Matrix # TK-614-A-3
          T.K. Records
        - KC and the Sunshine Band - Do you wanna go party, 1979; SR-24293; KC and the Sunshine Band (Box 44)
          Catalog # 611; A-side Matrix # TK-611-A
        - KDD - Opte pour le k (disc one), 1995; SR-24294; KDD (Box 44)
          In same jacket as # SR-24295. Double album.
          Catalog # COL 483 703-1; A-side Matrix # KDD-LP-A
        - KDD - Opte pour le k (disc two), 1995; SR-24295; KDD (Box 44)
          In same jacket as # SR-24294. Double album.
          Catalog # COL 483 703-1; A-side Matrix # KDD-LP-C
        - Kelis - Kaleidoscope (disc one), 1999; SR-24296; Kelis (Box 44)
          In same jacket as # SR-24297. Double album.
          Catalog # 7243 8 47911 1 7; A-side Matrix # V1-7243-8-47911-1-7-B
          Virgin
        - Kelis - Kaleidoscope (disc two), 1999; SR-24297; Kelis (Box 44)
          In same jacket as # SR-24296. Double album.
          Catalog # 7243 8 47911 1 7; A-side Matrix # V1-7243-8-47911-1-7-D
        - Kelly, R - R. Kelly (disc one), 1995; SR-24298; Kelly, R (Box 44)
          In same jacket as # SR-24299. Double album.
          Catalog # HIP 166; A-side Matrix # HIP166 A1
        - Kelly, R - R. Kelly (disc two), 1995; SR-24299; Kelly, R (Box 44)
          In same jacket as # SR-24298. Double album.
          Catalog # HIP 166; A-side Matrix # HIP166 C1
        - Kelly, Roberta - Gettin' the spirit, 1978; SR-24300; Kelly, Roberta (Box 44)
          Catalog # NBLP 7089; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7089-AS
        - Kendricks, Eddie - For you, 1974; SR-24301; Kendricks, Eddie (Box 44)
          Catalog # T6-335S1; A-side Matrix # T6335S1-D5RS-7815-1
          Tamla
        - Kendricks, Eddie - Ain't no smoke without fire, 1978; SR-24302; Kendricks, Eddie (Box 44)
          In same jacket as # SR-24303. Different discs.
          Catalog # SP-15; A-side Matrix # 2570-S
        - Kendricks, Eddie - Something more, 1979; SR-24303; Kendricks, Eddie (Box 44)
          In same jacket as # SR-24302. Different discs.
          Catalog # AB 4250; A-side Matrix # AB-4250-SA 1
        - Kenlou - Gimme groove; The bounce, 1995; SR-24304; Kenlou (Box 44)
          Catalog # MAW 0003; A-side Matrix # MAW-0003-A EUROPA DISK DMM NY USA 12330
          MAW Records
          Union City, New Jersey
        - Kennedy, Ed - Ed Kennedy, 1973; SR-24305; Kennedy, Ed (Box 44)
          Catalog # BLP-80122; A-side Matrix # STLP-80122-A
          Beverly
          Brazil
        - Keoki - Majick, 1997; SR-24306; Keoki (Box 44)
          Catalog # MM 88434-1; A-side Matrix # S-35086
          Moonshine Music
        - Kershaw, Doug - Instant hero, 1981; SR-24307; Kershaw, Doug (Box 44)
          Catalog # AL 37428; A-side Matrix # PAL-37428 1DF4
          Scotti Bros Records
        - Keys, Alicia - Little drummer girl; My younger days, 1996; SR-24308; Keys, Alicia; Lorenz, Trey (Box 44)
          Catalog # CAS 9218; A-side Matrix # XSS-9218A-1B
          So So Def
        - Khaled - Chebba, 1988; SR-24309; Khaled (Box 44)
          Catalog # 1598576; A-side Matrix # 159857 6 A 1
          Pathé Marconi
        - Khaled, Cheb - Hada raykoum, 1985; SR-24310; Khaled, Cheb; Khaled (Box 44)
          Catalog # 61198-1; A-side Matrix # MCPE 331198 A
        - Khaled, Cheb - Moule el kouchi, 1985; SR-24313; Khaled, Cheb; Khaled (Box 44)
          Catalog # 61216-1; A-side Matrix # 61216-1 A
        - Khan, Chaka - Clouds, 1980; SR-24311; Khan, Chaka (Box 44)
          Catalog # PRO-A-862; A-side Matrix # PROA1-862-S-A1
        - Khan, Chaka - Naughty, 1980; SR-24312; Khan, Chaka (Box 44)
          Catalog # BSK 3385; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3385-LW-2
        - Khan, Chaka - What cha' gonna do for me, 1981; SR-24314; Khan, Chaka (Box 44)
          In same jacket as # SR-24315. 2 copies.
          Catalog # HS 3526; A-side Matrix # HS-1-3526-WW2
        - Khan, Chaka - What cha' gonna do for me, 1981; SR-24315; Khan, Chaka (Box 44)
          In same jacket as # SR-24314. 2 copies.
        - Khan, Chaka - I feel for you, 1984; SR-25004; Khan, Chaka (Box 44)
          Catalog # 1-25162; A-side Matrix # 1-25162-A-SR2
        - Kid Creole and the Coconuts - Wise guy, 1982; SR-24317; Kid Creole and the Coconuts (Box 44)
          Catalog # SRK-3681; A-side Matrix # SRK-1-3681-RE1-LW2
        - Kid Creole and the Coconuts - Fresh fruit in foreign places, 1981; SR-24318; Kid Creole and the Coconuts (Box 44)
          Catalog # SRK 3534; A-side Matrix # SRK-1-3534-JW1
        - Kid Creole and the Coconuts - Maladie d'amour, 1980; SR-24319; Kid Creole and the Coconuts (Box 44)
          Catalog # AN 804; A-side Matrix # AN 804 A-1A
        - Kid Flash - He's in effect, 1988; SR-24320; Kid Flash (Box 44)
          Catalog # Z 44085; A-side Matrix # AL 44085-1A
          Tabu Records
        - Kid 'N Play - Kid 'N Play's funhouse, 1990; SR-24321; Kid 'N Play (Box 45)
          Catalog # SEL 21638; A-side Matrix # SEL 21638A-2
          Select Records
        - Kid Seville - Do you have a car?, 1984; SR-24322; Kid Seville (Box 45)
          Catalog # SG 428; A-side Matrix # SG-428-A-1
        - Kiddo - Try my loving (gimme just enough), 1983; SR-24324; Kiddo (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24325. Different discs.
          Catalog # SP-12055; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012055-A-S-RE1-P3
        - Kiddo - Kiddo, 1983; SR-24325; Kiddo (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24324. Different discs.
          Catalog # SP-6-4924; A-side Matrix # SP-064924A-RE2-ES1
        - Kids at Work - Kids at Work, 1984; SR-24323; Kids at Work (Box 45)
          Catalog # BFZ 39485; A-side Matrix # AL-39485-1A
          CBS Associated Records
        - Kids at Work - Togetherness, 1986; SR-24326; Kids at Work (Box 45)
          Catalog # RT002; A-side Matrix # RT-00002-A
          Rooftop Records
        - Kids From Fame - The Kids From Fame, 1982; SR-24327; Kids From Fame (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24328. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AFL1-4259; A-side Matrix # AFL1 4259 A 15
        - Kids From Fame - The Kids From Fame, 1982; SR-24328; Kids From Fame (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24327. 2 copies.
        - Kids in the Kitchen - Kids in the Kitchen, 1986; SR-24329; Kids in the Kitchen (Box 45)
          Catalog # 1-25377; A-side Matrix # 1 25377A SR2
        - Kihn, Greg - Love never fails, 1983; SR-24330; Kihn, Greg; Greg Kihn Band (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24331. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ED 4913; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-0-67913-A-LONG-2
          Beserkley
        - Kihn, Greg - Love never fails, 1983; SR-24331; Kihn, Greg; Greg Kihn Band (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24330. 2 copies.
        - Killing Joke - What's this for...!, 1981; SR-24332; Killing Joke (Box 45)
          Catalog # EGM 111; A-side Matrix # EGM-111-A
          Malicious Damage
        - Kilo Ali - Show me love, 1997; SR-24333; Kilo Ali (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24334. 2 copies.
          Catalog # INT12-95008; A-side Matrix # INT12-95008-A
          Organized Noize
          United States
        - Kilo Ali - Show me love, 1997; SR-24334; Kilo Ali (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24333. 2 copies.
        - Kim, Andy - Andy Kim's greatest hits, 1974; SR-24335; Kim, Andy (Box 45)
          Catalog # DSDP-50193; A-side Matrix # DSDP-50193-A
          Dunhill
        - Kinkina - Jungle fever, 1981; SR-24336; Kinkina (Box 45)
          Catalog # PRO 7008; A-side Matrix # PRO-7008A-1
        - King, BB - Midnight believer, 1978; SR-24337; King, BB (Box 45)
          Catalog # AA-1061; A-side Matrix # AA1061 A
          ABC Records
        - King, Ben E - Music trance, 1979; SR-24338; King, Ben E (Box 45)
          Catalog # DSKO 225; A-side Matrix # ST-DK-37813-1
        - King, Ben E - Music trance, 1980; SR-24339; King, Ben E (Box 45)
          Catalog # SD 19269; A-side Matrix # ST-A-804477-C
        - King, Carole - Her greatest hits (songs of long ago), 1978; SR-24340; King, Carole (Box 45)
          Catalog # JE 34967; A-side Matrix # PAL 34967-3D
          Ode Records
        - King Crimson - Discipline, 1981; SR-24341; King Crimson (Box 45)
          Catalog # BSK 3629; A-side Matrix # BSK-1 3629-S3
        - King Crimson - Beat, 1982; SR-24342; King Crimson (Box 45)
          Catalog # 2311 156; A-side Matrix # 176 2311156 1 380
          EG
        - King, Evelyn Champagne - Love come down, 1982; SR-24343; King, Evelyn Champagne (Box 45)
          Catalog # JD-13274; A-side Matrix # PD13274A 2
        - King, Evelyn Champagne - Out there; Make up your mind, 1979; SR-24344; King, Evelyn Champagne (Box 45)
          Catalog # JD-11681; A-side Matrix # PD-11681A-1
        - King, Evelyn Champagne - I'm in love, 1981; SR-24345; King, Evelyn Champagne (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24346. Different discs.
          Catalog # AFL1-3962; A-side Matrix # AFL-1-3962-A-1
        - King, Evelyn Champagne - Spirit of the dancer, 1981; SR-24346; King, Evelyn Champagne (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24345. Different discs.
          Catalog # JD-13018; A-side Matrix # PD-13018-A
        - King, Evelyn Champagne - Smooth talk, 1977; SR-24347; King, Evelyn Champagne (Box 45)
          Catalog # APL1-2466; A-side Matrix # APL1-2466A-1
        - King Floyd - Heart of the matter, 1971; SR-24348; King Floyd (Box 45)
          Catalog # VIPS-407; A-side Matrix # VIPS-407
          V.I.P.
        - King Hannibal - Truth, 1973; SR-24349; King Hannibal (Box 45)
          Catalog # AWLP 1001; A-side Matrix # 7115-291
          Aware
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - King, Marva - Feels right, 1981; SR-24350; King, Marva (Box 45)
          Catalog # P-16; A-side Matrix # P16-A-SH-1AR
          Planet Records
        - King Mellow Yellow - King Yellow Mellow meet Yellowman, 1982; SR-24351; King Mellow Yellow; Yellowman (Box 45)
          Catalog # J-385; A-side Matrix # YELLOWMAN-B
          Jam Rock
        - King Short Shirt - Ghetto vibes, 1978; SR-24352; King Short Shirt (Box 45)
          Catalog # CR 103; A-side Matrix # A+B-103-A
          Charlie's Records
        - King Tutt - Comin' out; Even though, 1980; SR-24353; King Tutt (Box 45)
          Catalog # 458; A-side Matrix # TKD-458-A
        - Kinney, Fern - Groove me, 1979; SR-24354; Kinney, Fern (Box 45)
          Catalog # 6361; A-side Matrix # M-6361-A-AM
          Malaco Records
        - Kiss - The Kiss album, 1978; SR-24355; Kiss (Box 45)
          Catalog # NBD 20137; A-side Matrix # NBD-20137-AS-P1
        - Kissing The Pink - Big man restless, 1983; SR-24356; Kissing The Pink (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24357. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DMD 654; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-45091-2
        - Kissing The Pink - Big man restless, 1983; SR-24357; Kissing The Pink (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24356. 2 copies.
        - Kissoon, Mac and Katie - Mac and Katie Kissoon, 1969; SR-24358; Kissoon, Mac and Katie (Box 45)
          Catalog # SHM 877; A-side Matrix # SHM877-A1
          Hallmark Records
        - Kitajima, Osamu - Dragon king, 1981; SR-24359; Kitajima, Osamu (Box 45)
          Catalog # AL 9570; A-side Matrix # AL-9570-SA
        - Kitch - The roots of soca, 1983; SR-24360; Kitch; Kitchener, Lord (Box 45)
          Catalog # KCR-334; A-side Matrix # KCR-338-B
        - Kitchener, Lord - Carnival fever, 1975; SR-24361; Kitchener, Lord (Box 45)
          Catalog # TRCS-4000; A-side Matrix # TRCS-4000-S1
          Trinidad Records
          Trinidad
        - Kitchener, Lord - The master at work, 1984; SR-24362; Kitchener, Lord (Box 45)
          Catalog # BB-136; A-side Matrix # 136-A
          Kalico Records
        - Kitch - Spirit of the Carnival, 1978; SR-24363; Kitch; Kitchener, Lord (Box 45)
          Catalog # CR 364; A-side Matrix # CR-364-A
        - Kitchener, Lord - We walk 100 miles with 'Kitch', 1974; SR-24364; Kitchener, Lord (Box 45)
          Catalog # TRCS-0003; A-side Matrix # TRCS-0003-S1
        - Klark Teknik - Overdub; She wants, 1996; SR-24365; Klark Teknik (Box 45)
          Catalog # AMTRAX 107; A-side Matrix # AMTRAX 107-A2
          Amtrax
        - Kleeer - Keeep your body workin', 1978; SR-24366; Kleeer (Box 45)
          Catalog # DSKO 148; A-side Matrix # ST-DSKO-36425-1
        - Kleeer - Intimate connection, 1984; SR-24367; Kleeer (Box 45)
          Catalog # 80145-1; A-side Matrix # STA-845387-A
        - Kleeer - Get ready, 1982; SR-24368; Kleeer (Box 45)
          Catalog # 80038-1; A-side Matrix # STA825093-A
        - Kleeer - Running back to you, 1981; SR-24369; Kleeer (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24370. Different discs.
          Catalog # DMD 275; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-39302-1
        - Kleeer - License to dream, 1981; SR-24370; Kleeer (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24369. Different discs.
          Catalog # SD 19288; A-side Matrix # ST-A-804571-A
        - Klique - I can't shake this feeling, 1982; SR-24371; Klique (Box 45)
          Catalog # L33-1773; A-side Matrix # MCA-3137
        - Klique - It's winning time, 1980; SR-24372; Klique (Box 45)
          Catalog # MCA-5198; A-side Matrix # MCA 2579-AM2
        - Klockwurk - Get up outcha seat (gonna get funky), 1981; SR-24373; Klockwurk (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24374. 2 copies.
          Catalog # RRD-2202; A-side Matrix # MF
          Red Rooster Records
        - Klockwurk - Get up outcha seat (gonna get funky), 1981; SR-24374; Klockwurk (Box 45)
          In same jacket as # SR-24373. 2 copies.
        - Klymaxx - Meeting in the ladies room, 1984; SR-24375; Klymaxx (Box 45)
          Catalog # MCA-5529; A-side Matrix # MCA-4984-FDS-2
          Constellation
        - Klymaxx - Klymaxx, 1986; SR-24399; Klymaxx (Box 45)
          Catalog # MCA-5832; A-side Matrix # MCA-5952-FDS-1
        - Klymaxx - Klymaxx, 1986; SR-24377; Klymaxx (Box 46)
        - Klymaxx - Girls will be girls, 1982; SR-24378; Klymaxx (Box 46)
          Catalog # 60177; A-side Matrix # 60177-A
          Solar
        - Klymaxx - Never underestimate the power of a woman, 1981; SR-24379; Klymaxx (Box 46)
          Catalog # S-21; A-side Matrix # S-21-A
        - Knack - Round trip, 1981; SR-24380; Knack (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24381. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ST-12168; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12168-Z16
          Capitol Records
        - Knack - Round trip, 1981; SR-24381; Knack (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24380. 2 copies.
        - Knight, Gladys - Miss Gladys Knight, 1978; SR-24382; Knight, Gladys (Box 46)
          Catalog # BDS 5714; A-side Matrix # BDS-5714-A-RE
        - Knight, Gladys - About love, 1980; SR-24383; Knight, Gladys; Gladys Knight and the Pips (Box 46)
          Catalog # AL 36387; A-side Matrix # AL 36387-1H
        - Knight, Gladys - Touch, 1981; SR-24384; Knight, Gladys; Gladys Knight and the Pips (Box 46)
          Catalog # AL 37086; A-side Matrix # PAL 37086 1B
        - Knight, Gladys - Visions, 1983; SR-24385; Knight, Gladys; Gladys Knight and the Pips (Box 46)
          Catalog # AL 38205; A-side Matrix # PAL-38205
        - Knight, Jean - Keep it comin', 1981; SR-24386; Knight, Jean; Premium (Box 46)
          Catalog # SD 5230; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN-814829-C
        - Knuckleheads - Tech's groove, 1998; SR-24387; Knuckleheads (Box 46)
          Catalog # BB-700; A-side Matrix # 9907X15-A
          Baltimore Breakbeat Records
        - Koffee Brown - Mars/Venus (disc one), 2001; SR-24388; Koffee Brown (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24389. Double album.
          Catalog # 07822-14662-1; A-side Matrix # 07822-14662-1A
        - Koffee Brown - Mars/Venus (disc two), 2001; SR-24389; Koffee Brown (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24388. Double album.
          Catalog # 07822-14662-1; A-side Matrix # 07822-14662-1C
        - KoKo-PoP - KoKo-PoP, 1984; SR-24390; KoKo-PoP (Box 46)
          Catalog # 6096ML; A-side Matrix # 6096ML-A-15B
        - Kokomo - Kokomo, 1982; SR-24391; Kokomo (Box 46)
          Catalog # FC 37937; A-side Matrix # PAL-37937
        - Kokomo - Kokomo, 1982; SR-24392; Kokomo (Box 46)
        - Kongas - Anikana-O, 1978; SR-24393; Kongas (Box 46)
          Catalog # SA 8512; A-side Matrix # SA 8512A
        - Kool & The Gang - Hangin' out; Ladies night, 1979; SR-24394; Kool & The Gang (Box 46)
          Catalog # DDS-502; A-side Matrix # 2-55992-DDS-502-A-1
          De-Lite Records
        - Kool & The Gang - Spirit of the boogie, 1975; SR-24395; Kool & The Gang (Box 46)
          Catalog # DEP 2016; A-side Matrix # DEP 2016 RM-A 7-24-75
        - Kool & The Gang - Steppin' out, 1981; SR-24396; Kool & The Gang (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24396. Different discs.
          Catalog # MK 186; A-side Matrix # MK-186-2-56476-PRC-C1-1
        - Kool & The Gang - Something special, 1981; SR-24397; Kool & The Gang (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24395. Different discs.
          Catalog # DSR-8502; A-side Matrix # DSR-8502-AS-K1
        - Kool & The Gang - Ladies night, 1979; SR-24398; Kool & The Gang (Box 46)
          Catalog # MK-108; A-side Matrix # MK-108 A1
        - Kool & The Gang - In the heart, 1983; SR-24400; Kool & The Gang (Box 46)
          Catalog # DSR- 8508; A-side Matrix # DSR-8508-AS-HRM1
        - Kool & The Gang - Everything is Kool & the Gang - greatest hits & more, 1988; SR-24401; Kool & The Gang (Box 46)
          Catalog # 422 834 780-1; A-side Matrix # 422-834-780-1-AS-SP-DMM
          Mercury
        - Kool Moe Dee - How ya like me now, 1987; SR-24402; Kool Moe Dee (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24403. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 1079-1-J; A-side Matrix # 1079-1-J-A
        - Kool Moe Dee - How ya like me now, 1987; SR-24403; Kool Moe Dee (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24402. 2 copies.
        - Kraftwerk - Electric cafe, 1986; SR-24404; Kraftwerk (Box 46)
          Catalog # 1-25525; A-side Matrix # B-25283-SH2
        - Kraftwerk - Kraftwerk's disco best, 1978; SR-24405; Kraftwerk (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24406. Different discs.
          Catalog # SPRO-8865; A-side Matrix # SPRO-8865 F1
        - Kraftwerk - Trans-Europe express, 1977; SR-24406; Kraftwerk (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24405. Different discs.
          Catalog # SPRO-8638; A-side Matrix # SPRO-8638-F2
        - Kravitz, Lenny - It ain't over 'til it's over, 1991; SR-24407; Kravitz, Lenny (Box 46)
          Catalog # VUST 43; A-side Matrix # VUST 43 A-1U-1-1
        - Kreem Team - Three hots and a cot, 1996; SR-24408; Kreem Team; Boosta Brody (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24409. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AR-82329; A-side Matrix # DRP 9602 A
          Action Recordings
        - Kreem Team - Three hots and a cot, 1996; SR-24409; Kreem Team; Boosta Brody (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24408. 2 copies.
        - Kriminal Base - The kaper, 1998; SR-24410; Kriminal Base (Box 46)
          Catalog # PP 003; A-side Matrix # PP 003 A
          Poop! Productions
        - KromOzone Project - Energy, 2000; SR-24411; KromOzone Project (Box 46)
          Catalog # KZ33390; A-side Matrix # KZ 33390-A
          TBC Productions
          Tampa, Florida
        - Krown Rulers - Paper chase, 2006; SR-24412; Krown Rulers (Box 46)
          Catalog # WAR-2707; A-side Matrix # WAR 2707 A
          Warlock Records
        - KRS One - The sneak attack (disc one), 2001; SR-24413; KRS One (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24414. Double album.
          Catalog # KOC-LP-8242; A-side Matrix # 25-KOC-LP-8242-1 A
          Koch Records
        - KRS One - The sneak attack (disc two), 2001; SR-24414; KRS One (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24413. Double album.
          Catalog # KOC-LP-8242; A-side Matrix # 25-KOC-LP-8242-1 C
        - KRS One - Illegal business remix 2004, 2003; SR-24415; KRS One (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24416. Different discs.
          Catalog # GRI 007; A-side Matrix # GRI-007-1A
          Grit Records
          Boston, Massachusettes
        - Various - Chicken scratch volume 20, 2003; SR-24416 (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24415. Different discs.
          Catalog # CS-20; A-side Matrix # CS-20 A1
          Chicken Scratch
        - Kula Shaker - Govinda, 1996; SR-24417; Kula Shaker (Box 46)
          Catalog # XPR 2324; A-side Matrix # 31 2324 20 1A1
          Sony Music Entertainment
        - Kwamé - The boy genius, 1989; SR-24418; Kwamé; A New Beginning (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24419. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 81941-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-887245-E
        - Kwamé - The boy genius, 1989; SR-24419; Kwamé; A New Beginning (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24418. 2 copies.
        - Kwick - To the point, 1981; SR-24420; Kwick (Box 46)
          Catalog # ST-17048; A-side Matrix # ST-1-17048-Z1
        - Kwick - Nightlife, 1981; SR-24421; Kwick (Box 46)
          Catalog # SPRO-9676; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9676-Z2
        - L.A. Boppers - Bop time!, 1981; SR-24422; L.A. Boppers (Box 46)
          Catalog # SRM-1-4006; A-side Matrix # SRM-1-4006AS
        - L.A. Dream Team - Kings of the west coast, 1986; SR-24423; L.A. Dream Team (Box 46)
          Catalog # MCA-5779; A-side Matrix # MCA 5618 FDS-4
        - L.A. Dream Team - Bad to the bone, 1987; SR-24424; L.A. Dream Team (Box 46)
          Catalog # MCA-42042; A-side Matrix # MCA-7021-FDS-1
        - L.A. Dream Team - Rockberry jam with funky fresh, 1985; SR-24425; L.A. Dream Team (Box 46)
          Catalog # DTR-630; A-side Matrix # DTR630-RE-ROCK SIDE
          Dream Team Records
        - La Funk Mob - Tribulations extra sensorielles (disc two), 1994; SR-24426; La Funk Mob (Box 46)
          Catalog # MW 017; A-side Matrix # MW 017 C1
          Mo Wax
        - La Funk Mob - Tribulations extra sensorielles (disc one), 1994; SR-24427; La Funk Mob (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24428; SR-24429. Different discs.
          Catalog # MW 017; A-side Matrix # MW 017 A1
        - La Funk Mob - Casse les frontières, fou les têtes en l'air (disc one), 1994; SR-24428; La Funk Mob (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24427; SR-24429. Double album.
          Catalog # MW 023; A-side Matrix # MW-023-A
        - La Funk Mob - Casse les frontières, fou les têtes en l'air (disc two), 1994; SR-24429; La Funk Mob (Box 46)
          In same jacket as # SR-24427; SR-24428. dOUble album.
          Catalog # MW 023; A-side Matrix # MW-023-C
        - Lab Rat - Carnivorous lunar activites, 1997; SR-24430; Lab Rat (Box 46)
          Catalog # HAND 039; A-side Matrix # HAND 039 T A1
          Hard Hands
        - LaBelle, Patti - The best of Patti LaBelle, 1982; SR-24431; LaBelle, Patti (Box 46)